<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pokemon</string>
    <!-- APP STRINGS RES -->
    <string name="title_first">30 Gen I Pokémons —</string>
    <string name="title_second">That you need to know</string>
    <string name="thirty_days">30 days</string>
    <string name="type">TYPE</string>
    <string name="weaknesses">WEAKNESSES</string>
    <string name="stats_percentage">%d\%%</string>
    <string name="stats">STATS</string>
    <string name="hp">HP</string>
    <string name="ap">AP</string>
    <string name="df">DF</string>
    <string name="single_digit">0%d</string>


    <!-- POKEMON NAMES -->
    <string name="bulbasaur">Bulbasaur</string>
    <string name="ivysaur">Ivysaur</string>
    <string name="venusaur">Venusaur</string>
    <string name="charmander">Charmander</string>
    <string name="charmeleon">Charmeleon</string>
    <string name="charizard">Charizard</string>
    <string name="squirtle">Squirtle</string>
    <string name="wartortle">Wartortle</string>
    <string name="blastoise">Blastoise</string>
    <string name="caterpie">Caterpie</string>
    <string name="metapod">Metapod</string>
    <string name="butterfree">Butterfree</string>
    <string name="weedle">Weedle</string>
    <string name="kakuna">Kakuna</string>
    <string name="beedrill">Beedrill</string>
    <string name="pidgey">Pidgey</string>
    <string name="pidgeotto">Pidgeotto</string>
    <string name="pidgeot">Pidgeot</string>
    <string name="rattata">Rattata</string>
    <string name="raticate">Raticate</string>
    <string name="spearow">Spearow</string>
    <string name="fearow">Fearow</string>
    <string name="ekans">Ekans</string>
    <string name="arbok">Arbok</string>
    <string name="pikachu">Pikachu</string>
    <string name="raichu">Raichu</string>
    <string name="sandshrew">Sandshrew</string>
    <string name="sandslash">Sandslash</string>
    <string name="nidoran">Nidoran</string>
    <string name="nidorina">Nidorina</string>

    <!-- POKEMON DESCRIPTIONS -->
    <string name="bulbasaur_description">
        There is a plant seed on its back right from the day this
        Pokémon is born. The seed slowly grows larger.
    </string>
    <string name="ivysaur_description">
        When the bulb on its back grows large, it appears to lose
        the ability to stand on its hind legs.
    </string>
    <string name="venusaur_description">
        Its plant blooms when it is absorbing solar energy.
        It stays on the move to seek sunlight.
    </string>
    <string name="charmander_description">
        It has a preference for hot things. When it rains,
        steam is said to spout from the tip of its tail.
    </string>
    <string name="charmeleon_description">
        It has a barbaric nature. In battle, it whips its fiery
        tail around and slashes away with sharp claws.
    </string>
    <string name="charizard_description">
        It spits fire that is hot enough to melt boulders.
        It may cause forest fires by blowing flames.
    </string>
    <string name="squirtle_description">
        When it retracts its long neck into its shell,
        it squirts out water with vigorous force.
    </string>
    <string name="wartortle_description">
        It is recognized as a symbol of longevity. If
        its shell has algae on it, that Wartortle is very old.
    </string>
    <string name="blastoise_description">
        It crushes its foe under its heavy body to cause fainting.
        In a pinch, it will withdraw inside its shell.
    </string>
    <string name="caterpie_description">
        For protection, it releases a horrible stench
        from the antenna on its head to drive away enemies.
    </string>
    <string name="metapod_description">
        It is waiting for the moment to evolve. At this stage,
        it can only harden, so it remains motionless to avoid attack.
    </string>
    <string name="butterfree_description">
        In battle, it flaps its wings at great speed to release highly
        toxic dust into the air.
    </string>
    <string name="weedle_description">
        Beware of the sharp stinger on its head. It hides in grass
        and bushes where it eats leaves.
    </string>
    <string name="kakuna_description">
        Able to move only slightly. When endangered, it may stick
        out its stinger and poison its enemy.
    </string>
    <string name="beedrill_description">
        It has three poisonous stingers on its forelegs and its tail.
        They are used to jab its enemy repeatedly.
    </string>
    <string name="pidgey_description">
        Very docile. If attacked, it will often kick up sand to
        protect itself rather than fight back.
    </string>
    <string name="pidgeotto_description">
        This Pokémon is full of vitality. It constantly flies around
        its large territory in search of prey.
    </string>
    <string name="pidgeot_description">
        This Pokémon flies at Mach 2 speed, seeking prey.
        Its large talons are feared as wicked weapons.
    </string>
    <string name="rattata_description">
        Will chew on anything with its fangs. If you see one,
        you can be certain that 40 more live in the area.
    </string>
    <string name="raticate_description">
        Its hind feet are webbed. They act as flippers,
        so it can swim in rivers and hunt for prey.
    </string>
    <string name="spearow_description">
        Inept at flying high. However, it can fly
        around very fast to protect its territory.
    </string>
    <string name="fearow_description">
        A Pokémon that dates back many years. If it senses
        danger, it flies high and away, instantly.
    </string>
    <string name="ekans_description">
        The older it gets, the longer it grows. At night,
        it wraps its long body around tree branches to rest.
    </string>
    <string name="arbok_description">
        The frightening patterns on its belly have been studied.
        Six variations have been confirmed.
    </string>
    <string name="pikachu_description">
        When it is angered, it immediately discharges the energy
        stored in the pouches in its cheeks.
    </string>
    <string name="raichu_description">
        Its tail discharges electricity into the ground, protecting
        it from getting shocked.
    </string>
    <string name="sandshrew_description">
        It loves to bathe in the grit of dry, sandy areas. By sand bathing,
        the Pokémon rids itself of dirt and moisture clinging to its body.
    </string>
    <string name="sandslash_description">
        The drier the area Sandslash lives in, the harder and smoother the
        Pokémon’s spikes will feel when touched.
    </string>
    <string name="nidoran_description">
        Females are more sensitive to smells than males. While foraging,
        they’ll use their whiskers to check wind direction and stay downwind of predators.
    </string>
    <string name="nidorina_description">
        The horn on its head has atrophied. It’s thought that this happens so Nidorina’s
        children won’t get poked while their mother is feeding them.
    </string>
</resources>